

# **NGUYEN VAN A**

## **MARKETING MANAGER**

Male

**May 19, 1992** 

♥ Hanoi, Vietnam

fb.com/quynhtom design

Take advantages of sales skills & experience and d tables. Those with an eye for detail may have caught a tribu of market to become a professional Sales Staff and bring a lot value to Customers. From that, I will contribute to development of CVPRO Company.

#### **EDUCATION**



#### **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. ationally e administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

#### **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. corporate administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

# **EXPERIENCE**



Sep 2007 - Present

#### **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

#### Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult ting type for a galley TYPESETTER SELECTING TYPE REMIXING A CLASSIC So how did and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

#### **Recognition and Gains:**

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

Sep 2007 - Present

#### **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

#### Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to he goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

Recognition and Gains:

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

# **ACTIVITIES**





#### Sale Executive

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer erived from Cicero's 1st-century BC text De Finibus Bonorum et Malorum. En' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

## **CERTIFICATIONS**



**TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO** 2004

# **HONORS & AWARDS**



**TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO** 2013 - 2014

# **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION**



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt scholarships and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US on tại năm thế kỉ, mà khi được áp dụng vào tin học văn phòng, nội dung của nó vẫn không hề b

#### **REFERENCES**



#### **NGUYEN VAN BINH**

director of cvpro jsc

**U** 01234567890 mbinhnv@topcv.com

## **SKILLS**



Words Photoshop Excel **English** Power Point • **Japanese** 

# **INTERESTS**



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt aut and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US universities